A Guide to the Marian Van Landigham Papers, 1979-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Subject Files, 1981-2006., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 16-24)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas - Nomination for Lt. Governor, 1985. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Woodrow Wilson Bridge. (Box 24, Folder 1-9)
- Series III. "White" Files, 1982-1987, 1992., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 25-26)
  The "white" files cover the years 1982 to 1987 and 1992, and are copies of outgoing letters from Van Landingham's office. They are arrranged by year, and thereunder alphabetical by last name of the recipient.
  - 1982 (A-K). (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1982 (L-Z). (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - November 1982 - November 1983. (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - 1984. (Box 25, Folder 6-8)
  - 1985. (Box 25, Folder 9-11)
  - August-December 1985. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1985-1986. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1986. (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - 1987. (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
  - 1992. (Box 26, Folder 8-10)
- Series IV. Campaign Files, 1979-1995., Extent: 1 box. (Box 27)
  The campaign files cover Van Landingham's race for Alexandria City Council in 1979, and her subsequent campaigns for the Virginia House of Delegates. They include campaign literature, meeting information, planning and budgeting files, clippings, contributions and financial reports, events and fundraisers, mailings, polling data, precinct maps, volunteer lists and other materials.
  - Baliles, Gerald L. - Congratulatory Letter, 1982. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Campaign, 1995. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Literature. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Logo. (Box 28)
  - Campaign Meetings, 1987. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Planning and Budgeting, 1983. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Poster. (Box Personal Papers Oversize Box 104)
  - Campaign T-Shirt and Apron. (Box 29)
  - City Council Race, 1979. (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
  - Clippings. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Contributions and Financial Reports, 1987. (Box 27, Folder 9-11)
  - Contributions and Financial Reports, 1993-1994. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, 1987. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Events/Fundraisers. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Mailings. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Mu Chapter, Delta Kappa Gamma - Directory, 1992-1994. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Polling, 1987. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Precinct Maps. (Box 28)
  - Questionnaire, 1987. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - "The Power of the Incumbency". (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Volunteers. (Box 27, Folder 20)